

PERSONAL PROFILE

An experienced Software Testing Professional with a solid foundation in Agile Software Development. Skilled in black box testing; user acceptance, regression, performance, stress testing. Applying my knowledge and skills in a corporate world of testing and delivering quality products.

SPECIALIZATIONS

Online Casino Games (Desktop, Mobile) Slot Machines 3D Printing (Software, Firmware) Desktop and Mobile Applications

COMPETENCIES

Adept in:

Software Testing (Functional, Nonfunctional), Sikuli X Automation tool, Python, JIRA, Confluence, Mantis, RDBMS, Postman, CRM

Currently Learning:

JMeter, Telerik Test Studio

Personal Skills:

Critical Thinking, Innovation, Creativity, Flexibility, Detail-oriented

CONTACT INFORMATION

Mobile: (+63) 956-904-9078

Email: sandymendoza2014@gmail.com

Skype: sandymendoza.29

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandymendoza/

Balayan, Batangas Philippines 4213

CHARACATER REFERENCE

Johnry Bautista

Spiralworks Incorporated Game Developer +63 908-355-3353

SANDY MENDOZA

SOFTWARE TESTING PROFESSIONAL

CAREER HISTORY

Manual Tester

Pro Source Global BPO Inc. | July 2019-present

- Verify acceptance criteria through User Stories
- Manage/monitor defects in JIRA and update the status in a timely manner
- Check whether the business requirements are met and no gaps during testing
- Perform E2E testing for COVID web and mobile apps
- Perform back-end testing using TOAD for MySQL
- Perform regression once bugs are resolved
- Identify bottlenecks in the entire testing phase

Quality Assurance

Xceed CCS under Skywind Group | May 2018-Jun 2019

- Tested Skywind casino games to check whether the business requirements and specifications are met
- Gathered requirements through BRD/FRD review or walkthrough meetings
- Designed, created and executed comprehensive test cases in JIRA
- Performed smoke and sanity tests before sending the build for further testing
- Documented relevant information on Confluence (BRD, specifications)
- Assisted the team lead in the test closure tasks
- Participated in test estimation, defect triage and sprint planning
- Server-related testing, Regulations testing, Localisation testing, E2E testing, Acceptance testing
- Attended game kickoff meetings

Software QA Engineer

Kinpo Electronics (XYZ Printing) | July 2016-May 2018

- Recorded the slicing time of 3d object and compare it to other 3d software
- Studied new software features to determine their functionalities
- Found and isolated bugs and report them to the Mantis bug tracking system Analysed issues and provide a detailed report to Test Lead
- Collaborated to the developers more often and listen to discussions
- Test case writing and estimation
- Performed regression when issues are resolved

QA Tester

Aruze Gaming America (Philippine Branch) | Jan 2015-May 2015

- Tested casino games to ensure that specification and requirements are met
- Strictly followed guidelines and documents related to the job (Manuals & checklists)
- Provided a test report to monitor the current status of the tests and tasks performed
- Created test schedule which will show the time frame and deadline to meet
- Explored, observed and stressed the game to its limit

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

STI College

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology | Jun 2009 - May 2014 Graduated with GWA: 1.63